PROFESSOR: I have one more thing
I want to tell you today.
And that is that, do not forget
that search operates over
models of the world.
The agent does not actually try out
all these things on the fringe.
None of these things happen.
This is in the agents head.
Planning is all in simulation.
And that means that your search is only
as good as your model, and you'll
discover whether or not your model is
good when you execute the search.
So it is only a model.
Let me show you the consequences
of this.
And that is--
you've probably used something like
Google Maps or MapQuest to route,
here's a case where you get back a
route, you go down Glendale Boulevard,
and you make a right onto
Loma Vista Place.
And that seems perfectly reasonable
looking at the map.
And then, in practice, you look at
Loma Vista, and there it is.
Make a right on Loma Vista.
OK, was this an incorrect
search problem?
OK, the search solution is perfectly
reasonable, what went wrong here?
The model, right?
The model says this is a road that you
can use, and, in fact, it's not.
So there's nothing wrong with the search
algorithm, it's the model.
How about this one?
This is going from Haugesund, Norway
to Trondheim, so from the
green to the red.
Now, the interesting part is rather
than going north from Haugesund to
Trondheim, you actually get in
a boat and go to England.
So unless you want your agents to end up
very, very, very confused when they
execute these plans, you need to make
sure that the models you pick as your
abstraction actually are safe, that they
work in the real world, that's
about formulation.
Next time we'll pick up with solution,
and think about ways we can take these
ideas about being guided towards
your solution to make
our search more efficient.